No ! I can 't concentrate .
Please , maestro I 'm sorry but ...
Let 's continue from number 37 .
Oh , my god ! No , no !
Maestro , please let 's take it from " Vieni Altrove "
Stop ! Stop !
I can 't stand it anymore !
- It 's ridiculous ! - Poor thing . Are you hurt ?
It 's ridiculous ! This is Macbeth by Giuseppe Verdi !
I 've never seen such lousy direction .
- Is there a problem ? - Yes , you director !
This isn 't one of your third rate movies !
Birds on stage , back projection , laser beams !
Is this an opera or amusement park ?
I have to sing ! How can I do that
with a raven on stage that hates me ?
Why would the raven hate you ?
It always looks at me with those eyes ..
It shrieks , whistles , flaps its wings .
It 's deliberately disturbs my performance
I won 't be back !
But it 's just an animal ...
That 's right !
Animals shouldn 't be at the Opera
singing Macbeth !
- Where is my manager ? - I 'm here Mara .
Where is my manager ? I am going back to the hotel .
- Please don 't be like this . - It 's 4 : 30 ...
I 'll rest until 7 : 00 and at 8 : 00 I 'll be ready to sing .
Without ravens or any other nonsense !
A real opera !
What do we do now ?
Let 's get on with the rehearsal .
If something like this happens again
I 'll take my ravens and leave .
OK .
Maestro ? Let 's get back to it .
We 'll take it from we left it .
This is all your fault
for such a bizarre and outrageous direction !
Ladies and gentlemen , the great Mara Chekova
Has been knocked down by a car !
Call an ambulance . Hurry !
Go ! Run ! Hurry !
Oh God ! Oh God ! What a disaster !
- Hello ? - Is that you , Betty ?
Yes .
Tonight you make your debut as Lady Macbeth .
- What ? - Are you happy ?
Who 's speaking ?
Is this a joke ?
Hello ?
Mira !
Come on , Betty .
Get ready , in exactly one hour , you 've got to be on stage .
Mara Chekova had an accident . Here .
Someone already called . I thought it was a joke .
Why are you crying ?
Are you scared of making your debut ?
No ! But I 'm too young for Lady Macbeth .
My voice isn 't right .
No , you 'll make a sensation !
I won 't be able to reach some of the notes .
- I can 't do it ! - Trust me .
I 'm not just your agent , I 'm also your friend .
I know what you 're going through .
Just stage fright .
Don 't let them see it .
They 're all here to see you .
Don 't show them your lack of confidence
All right ! I get it !
Well , my dear Betty , are we ready ?
Mara 's unfortunate accident is going
to speed you towards your destiny .
Tonight you will make your debut in Verdi 's Macbeth .
What are those tears ?
Tears of happiness , I hope .
Don 't tell me you 're afraid .
Afraid you 'll fail ?
I 'm too young for the role .
Did you know that Verdi 's first Lady Macbeth
was only 17 ?
Anyway , you know the opera by heart .
I watched you at all rehearsals . You worked so hard ...
As though you were the star and not the understudy .
Don 't worry about the orchestra .
They 'll only need half an hour 's rehearsal .
Excellent .
Come on . Stop it ! This is your big chance .
I know but ...
Think of how happy and proud
your mother would have been ...
if she saw you following in her footsteps .
That would have pleased her .
Believe me .
What happened to Chekova ?
She got hit by a car or so I heard .
Ah , you are listening to Prokofsky 's recording of Macbeth .
Did you know it was a production of ours ?
1975 .
It 's the opera . Macbeth brings bad luck .
What are you talking about ?
Everyone says it . It 's a beautiful opera but ...
it brings bad luck ...
I would much rather make my debut in something else .
Don 't let them hear you say that .
- But it 's true ! - Shut up !
So you think this opera brings bad luck ?
I don 't know . It 's what everyone says .
I don 't say it .
Listen , you have a wonderful voice .
You are very beautiful
and you 're lucky enough
to be making your debut in a great theater .
You should make the most of this opportunity .
These things usually only happen
to people in movies .
Just seize the opportunity and stop being silly .
OK .
Good call .
Six , five , four , three , two , one , now !
Let her through , let her through !
There 's too much smoke .
I said there 's too much smoke !
Dino , cut the smoke . Cut the smoke !
Wait a second . No ! The scar should be on the other side !
Betty goes on in two minutes !
Good , another two minutes for Betty .
Go back , hurry !
Betty , you 're on in two minutes .
Put it on better ! I told you to turn it !
Oh , what are you doing ? Leave it !
- Oh , no , stop it ! - It will be a success !
Break a leg !
That 's okay . I 'll just do it myself .
Be careful ! Don 't ruin the costume .
You 've finally returned .
What are you doing here ? You 're not allowed in here .
This box is for stage personnel only . Come on . Let 's go .
Are you mad ?
Betty , let 's continue .
Keep going !
It was an accident . Nothing more . Okay ?
Give it here .
All good , maestro .
Well done , Betty ! You 're so wonderful !
Enough ! Enough ! That idiot !
That 's enough , Mara ! Don 't be childish .
What a triumph ! You 're a star !
You really think so ?
Didn 't you hear the applause ?
Thank you .
Bravo . You 're wonderful ! Wonderful !
Congratulations ! . You were magnificent .
Thank you .
There 'll be a reception later on .
- Don 't miss it ! - Thank you .
- Betty , you were perfect . - I owe to you , maestro .
- Will I see you at the reception ? - Yes . Of course .
A real triumph !
Marc , the press are here .
Yes , there was an accident with the lights .
I hear shouting and screaming in the room !
What are you talking about , what screams ?
- You didn 't hear it ? - No .
Yes , it came from one of the boxes .
- Betty ? - Oh , Marc !
I know we 've had a little accident , but it 's got nothing to do with Macbeth .
The only bad luck Macbeth has brought you is fame .
My mother was a famous singer as well .
Betty , go change quickly .
People will be waiting for you . Hurry !
Fantastic !
Everything was perfect !
Betty , you were fantastic !
You were great !
I just love Verdi 's music . I really do !
You were wonderful . Just wonderful .
It 's just that damn , damn director !
I can 't take him anymore .
Giulia ?
You work here in the theater ?
No ... l ...
- You 're a fan of mine . - Yes .
The first .
- Sorry ? - My first ... fan .
Congratulations .
- Do you want an autograph ? - Oh , yeah .
- That 's very nice of you . Thank you . - Don 't mention it .
What name shall I write ? Excuse me .
Alan .
Alan ?
- Thank you . - Are you a foreigner ?
Oh , no .
Everything is ready , Inspector , and they 're all waiting for you .
Yes I 'm coming .
So you are a policeman , not a fan .
Can 't a policeman be a fan ? It 's just that ...
I 'm not an expert on opera but ...
Your voice is ...
Thanks for the autograph .
Yes ?
- Hi . - Hi .
- What did the cop want ? - Nothing , just my autograph .
But who knows what he is doing here ?
I don 't know . I have no idea .
Oh , maybe because of the accident
with the lights . One of the ushers died .
- What ? - Yes , it 's very strange .
Leave your costume there .
Marc says it needs a few alterations .
Listen Stefano , I don 't want to go to the party alone .
Would you come with me ?
- Please ? - Of course , I would love to !
I almost forgot . You were great tonight .
And it looks like I 'm the last one
to congratulate you .
So you think it would be okay if I had a kiss ?
Even if I 'm only the stage manager ?
Can I ?
Did you really like me ? Really ?
Like you ? I loved you ! You were great .
From the great Mara Chekova .
- With her best wishes . - Thank you .
The great Mara Chekova ..
We can say that she was literally struck
by the curse of Macbeth .
" Good luck , little snake . "
Bitch .
Hmm ... What is it ?
How should I know ?
- What do you think it is ? - Who knows ?
Snake venom ?
Acid ? Toad slime ?
Hey ! Stefano ! What 's wrong ?
What 's happening ? What 's happening ?
You idiot !
You scared me .
But what was it ?
Yuck ! Ginseng ! Chekova would bathe in that stuff !
Stop this racket !
Filthy damn birds !
No , it 's useless . I can 't . It 's not your fault .
I 'm a disaster in bed .
I don 't know why . I 'm sorry .
According to the legend
opera singers are incredibly horny .
I 'm serious . They say they make love
before they go on stage .
It makes the voice ...
The voice more relaxed ... free
Either I 'm a lousy opera singer ...
Or I am an exception .
- Have I offended you ? - No .
Well , I mean ... now that you 're famous
it seems that things have changed between us .
No , don 't say that .
It 's not true .
What a beautiful house !
It looks like a museum .
It sort of is . It 's my uncle 's .
He 's a bit crazy but he is really rich
and he lets me use it whenever I need it .
- Want some tea ? - Yes , please .
All right , I 've got rose , jasmine
- Or mint . - Jasmine .
Jasmine . Okay .
No ! Mint !
Take a good look . You can 't close your eyes .
You have to watch everything .
Everything .
Betty !
Why did you lock it ? Aren 't you feeling well ?
No , no !
What is going on Betty ?
Oh my God ...
It 's not true you 're frigid .
You 're a bitch on heat .
Hello ?
There 's been a murder .
At 66 Viale Pegaso .
Who 's speaking ?
My god ! Look what success has done to you !
Come on . I 'm gonna get the papers .
I want to read the reviews .
So ?
Is something wrong with your eyes ?
Can I know what 's wrong ?
Yes , the lights .
Oh come on , the lights ?
Okay , it wasn 't the lights .
How do you turn the heating on ?
I 'll do it .
So , will you tell me what happened ?
Nothing . Nothing happened .
It was so ...
No , I can 't tell you .
Trouble in love ?
Love ?
What love ?
Whenever a woman has a problem
men always assume it 's love .
You sopranos are famous for ...
For whoring around ?
No , wait a minute ... I didn 't mean that ...
Look , I 've already heard that story tonight .
There 's a bunch of people that think
that we singers ...
make love just before going on stage
to improve our voice .
It 's wrong . For me , anyway , it 's totally wrong .
I don 't understand why you 're so upset .
I don 't want to talk about it .
I don 't know ...
This whole thing just tires me .
Sorry but what 's it got to do with me ?
Why don 't we talk about you instead ?
You film people are known to be a depraved lot ...
Ah that 's for sure .
We only work if there is some spare time ...
Come on . You have to talk about it sooner or later .
And then I ran away , and that 's when I found you .
You see ...
The strangest thing about what happened tonight ...
All the terrible things I saw are part of a nightmare
I used to have as a child .
I used to dream of a man
wearing a black hood on his face .
Tonight I saw that same hood .
- You said you called the police . - Yes .
- Did you give your name ? - No .
Did you tell them everything ?
About what happened tonight ? Yes .
Why ? ls there anything else ?
I 'll check all the other rooms .
Have you got a boyfriend ?
- No . - Or someone
who might get jealous ?
No . No one that I know of . Why ?
There 's someone in the street
watching your windows with binoculars .
- Where ? - Come and see .
I don 't see anyone .
Ah , he 's gone .
He was there , next to the photo booth .
Betty , do you want me to stay ?
Don 't you have anyone jealous waiting for you ?
Yes ... But if you want ...
She must be upset that you 're not home yet .
I 'll lock myself in . Don 't worry .
Make sure you lock all the windows .
I 'll look around in the street .
If I see anything suspicious , I 'll call you .
If not ...
I 'll see you tomorrow .
What 's wrong ?
There are 2 people out there .
- Do you know them ? - No .
Who 's out there ?
Who are you ?
Who do you think it is , I live here !
I 'm your neighbour .
Who is that ? Was he looking for me ?
No .
Don 't be nosy .
Mind your own business .
Who are you looking for ?
Do you think it 's true ? I don 't know her .
Maybe she is saying the truth .
Close the door well . I don 't want to lose another Lady Macbeth .
Okay .
Who is it ?
Who 's there ?
Hello ?
Who is there ? Who is speaking ?
Marc ? Is that you ?
Oh , my god ! Why did I do it ?
I shouldn 't have accepted the role .
It 's all my fault .
Why , why did I do it ?
Don 't cry , Betty . Don 't cry .
" Hostile reception for Macbeth . "
" Brilliant debut by a young singer ...
who at the last moment substituted Mara Chekova "
" Sets were uselessly revolutionary . "
" Doubts regarding the direction . "
" Word to the director :
Go back to horror films . Forget opera . "
They 're tearing you to pieces .
Yes , but nicely .
And a total unknown gets all the praise .
Well , she was fantastic .
The last time they said
nice things about your singer
and criticised your direction of Rigoletto
you were furious , but not this time .
How come ?
Tell me the truth
do you want to take the girl to bed ?
Listen . To be here with you this evening ,
I took two flights and turned down a fashion show .
Fragments of the same feathers mixed with traces of blood ...
Were found on a carpet in Stefano Brini 's apartment .
He worked here as your ...
- Stage manager . - Yes . Stage manager .
He was killed , or rather ... butchered last night ,
Between 1 am and 2 am .
Who saw him last ?
Well , there was a first-night party .
Did he leave alone ?
I really don 't know . I wasn 't there .
Who else went to the party ? You ?
Yes .
At what time did he leave ? Was he alone ?
I think he left with Betty , our singer .
- Where is Betty ? - She should arrive soon .
We 're about to rehearse so if you don 't mind ...
Sorry , I 'm not done yet .
You 're Maurizio , right ?
Are you in charge of the ravens ?
- Yes . - How many were killed ?
Three , Inspector .
I think I know who killed my ravens .
- Who ? - Mara Chekova .
That lunatic hated them !
No . Maurizio , that 's nonsense .
Don 't be ridiculous .
Ravens are very vindictive .
They don 't forget .
They remember for years
and at the right moment , zap !
What do you think ?
There were many strange occurrences ...
during this performance ...
What a bore ...
and so many coincidences .
I don 't want you to think I 'm superstitious
But it 's Macbeth that brings bad luck .
Everyone knows that .
I could tell you about dozens of strange incidents .
A lot of people seriously believe
that the opera is jinxed .
I 've seen a lot of your movies .
You 're really an expert in this field .
I 'd be very interested to know your opinion .
I 'm sorry but I don 't see the point
in using movies to explain the reality .
Depends what you mean by reality .
Excuse me , but I 've got to fix this dress .
The next performance is in two days
and I only have a pair of hands .
Even if you had ten hands
that costume would still be a rag .
What ?
All right , Mr. Great Director !
I 'd put most of the blame
for what 's happening ...
On our fancy-pants , whimsical director here ...
who thinks Verdi and Shakespeare
were two incompetent idiots just like him .
I 'll fix the dress , all right , but not for you !
For Giuseppe Verdi !
- All this turns you on , doesn 't it ? - What are you talking about ?
- You 're a sadist . - Oh , really ?
Everyone I know who has worked with you says it .
If they say it , they 're wrong .
Giulia ?
Just the person I wanted to see .
- What 's happened to my costume ? - Look at this mess .
- Someone tore it apart . - Who could have done it ?
I don 't know ... someone who doesn 't like the opera ,
Or Marc 's dreadful representation .
That genius went over the top this time !
It 's not like in the movies
where when you come up with something original
everyone congratulates you .
God , what a mess ! Now , I need to fix it !
And since they didn 't call in the dressmaker
I need to do it myself !
I 'm sorry . You 'll have to try on again
once I 've finished .
We 're lucky , though .
The jewellery is still intact .
Listen , Giulia , I 'll be back in a minute .
Mira , I must see you now .
Me too . My phone hasn 't stopped ringing .
Everybody wants you . Rome ! Vienna ! Paris !
That 's wonderful
but I have to talk to you about something else .
Something really serious .
There 's a maniac who 's after me .
- I need your advice on what to do . - I 'll give it to you now .
- Call the police . - No , I can 't .
I 'm in terrible trouble
and I don 't know what to do .
Mira , I must see you . Come quick , please !
Yeah , all right . I 'll come by this evening .
But what 's going on ?
Betty ?
Is that you ?
Who is it ?
Oh it 's you ! You scared me !
Come here , look .
It was on your costume .
So ?
It 's gold ! I never sewed any real gold on this thing .
- Is it yours ? - No , I never saw it before .
- How did it get on my costume ? - Who knows ?
Maybe the one ripped up the dress dropped it .
Yes and it got caught in the sequins .
Give me that .
It looks like there 's something written on it ...
Maybe a name ...
A name ? Show me !
It 's unreadable . The letters are almost faded away .
Wait , I have a magnifying glass somewhere ...
Where did I see it ?
I can 't remember .
Ah yes !
It should be ...
- Any Luck ? - No !
I 'm sure I had seen it !
Wait , maybe it 's here .
Nothing , nothing ... It disappeared !
What happened ?
- Betty ! ? - I 'm all right !
Don 't worry !
No , no , it can 't be here .
I saw it in a drawer ...
Betty , you continue looking .
I 'll check if it 's over there .
I found it !
I found it .
You enjoyed it last night , you whore .
You opera singers are all whores .
There 's a date !
It has to be an anniversary .
Where are you ?
Betty !
Here ... Is this what you want ?
Is it this ?
It 's yours !
No , no !
It 's ...
I 'll take you whenever I want !
- Hi - Hi .
Let go of me ! Leave me alone !
This blood ... Who did this to you ?
It 's another proof of the curse of Macbeth ?
Or did it happen last night ?
So it did happen last night .
Yes !
Why didn 't you tell me ?
Because ...
It was terrible ...
It was worse than anything
I could ever have imagined .
I just wanted to forget , cancel it from my mind .
I didn 't want to watch ...
I didn 't want to feel anything ...
to think about anything !
I just wanted to get away !
I understand what you 're saying .
Listen , I 'm here to help you
not to persecute you .
The police should stop criminals .
But I need your help .
Trust me .
I don 't know what he looks like .
He ties me up .
Touches me .
He forces me to watch .
But he never lets me see his face .
This afternoon ...
At the theater
He killed Giulia the wardrobe mistress .
- What ? I 'll go over there now . - No , please !
Don 't worry . We 'll get to the bottom of this . I 'll be back .
Don 't leave me alone .
I 'm afraid . Please .
Ok , let 's do it this way ...
You go home and lock yourself in .
I 'll send my assistant , Daniele Soave .
All right .
Daniele Soave , a capable young man .
- Who is it ? - It 's Daniele Soave
did the Inspector tell you about me coming ?
Yes , yes , please come up .
Good evening . May I come in ?
Yes , of course , please .
Don 't worry about me .
My eyes hurt , so I put some drops in them .
May I take a look around ?
Yeah , go ahead .
Just give me a minute , I 'll be with you shortly .
- Are you nervous ? - A little .
- No , a lot . - I 'm here now , you can relax .
Thank you but I have a great system for relaxing .
You are feeling very calm .
Calm and relaxed .
Concentrate only on the music .
Breathe deeply .
One ,
Two ,
Three , four .
- Did you call me ? - No .
I 'm listening to a tape .
If you need me , I 'm in the living room .
I 'll get it .
Are you expecting someone ?
Yes , a friend .
Check who it is before opening the door .
Of course , but I know it 's her .
Is that you , Mira ?
It 's her .
I read the papers .
How terrible !
And it 's getting worse .
Keep your voice down .
- Is someone here ? - Yes !
Touring in Paris and Vienna my foot !
The lunatic killed again this afternoon .
Giulia , the wardrobe mistress .
I was there .
Now I understand why the police
are keeping an eye on you .
- Who told you that ? - What ?
How do you know the police is keeping an eye ?
The officer downstairs in the hall .
They asked me who I was , where I was going .
His name is ... Soave .
- You mean Daniele Soave ? - Yeah , that 's right .
But he 's in the living room .
How could he be in the living room ? Betty it 's impossible .
Come with me .
He was here , I 'm sure .
- Then who is he ? - I don 't know .
He could be the maniac !
He 's gone . He was in there !
Call the police !
The phone 's over there .
I 'm too scared to go in .
He may be hiding , waiting ...
Let 's get out of here !
Wait .. Listen ..
What if the one downstairs is the maniac ?
And what if it 's the other way around ?
I don 't want to find out either way .
You 're right .
I didn 't even get a good look at him .
The kitchen ! It 's a strong door .
The knives ! We can defend ourselves .
I 'd like to see him get in here now . Bastard !
We can always scream .
You 're a singer . If you scream , they will hear us !
It 's pointless , this building is ancient .
The walls are too thick . No one will hear a thing .
Yes . Yes .
Right . All right .
Open this door ! It 's me , Daniele Soave .
He 's outside .
The Maniac is inside !
Hurry , open the door !
I 'm with the police . Open !
I don 't trust you ? You could be the maniac .
I 'll show you my identification .
Here , do you see it ?
- No , I can 't see ! - Just a minute !
Here , do you see it now ?
Anyone can get one . It 's a fake .
It 's not fake !
Come on , let me in !
No , you 're fooling me . Go away !
Look , my police gun . It 's proof no ?
I 've seen you before . I know you !
Let me in !
- No ! - I have the gun !
I want to see your face again !
Come on Betty .
You may as well open the door now .
One way or another , I 'm coming in !
You bastard !
Son of a bitch !
I am going to kill you !
You 're not going to get me ! You 're not !
I 'll kill you !
You are feeling very calm .
Calm and relaxed .
Concentrate only on the music .
Breathe deeply .
One , two , three ,
Four .
Daniele Soave .
So he was the policeman .
Betty ! Betty ! Come on . Come on !
Quickly ! Quickly , climb up here . Quickly !
- Where does this lead to ? - To my apartment .
What were you doing in here ?
I discovered it . It 's the old air-conditioning system .
I can get to any apartment .
Once I saw the shadow of a man crawling
I was scared !
- Who was it ? - I don 't know .
This apartment is empty .
- I watch you all the time . - Really ?
Yes . I like it when you sing .
- You have a beautiful voice . - Thank you .
Why did he want to kill you ?
I don 't know ... But why do you come here alone ?
I come here to get away when my parents hit each other .
- Hit each other ? - Yes
Here we are .
He 's gone . You are very clever .
You 're the clever one . You saved my life .
Alma ?
It 's my mother .
Who is she ? What are you doing here ?
- Oh , I know her ! - Mom , this is Betty .
- Do you remember me ? - No , I don 't remember you .
Last night . You were outside my apartment .
True , you didn 't see me .
Listen , something terrible has happened .
Yeah , you coming in here .
Did you let her in , Alma ?
- Yes , she did . - She 's my friend .
- I have to call the police . - Get out of here .
- Don 't throw her out , she 's my friend . - I don 't care . Shut up !
- Please , where 's the phone ? - Didn 't you hear me ? Leave !
Get out !
All right , I 'm going . But you call the police !
You 're so filthy ! Disgusting !
You 're disgusting ! You 're always naked !
That 's enough ! Go to your room .
What are you doing here ?
Marc , did you hear what happened ?
Yes . I phoned your apartment .
I spoke to a policeman .
I didn 't think you 'd come here .
I just wanted to run , hide .
I didn 't know where to go .
And I don 't know how ...
I ended up here ...
I 'll sleep in my dressing room .
Oh , Betty ?
I 'm sorry but there 's going to be a lot of noise .
The stagehands are working .
- I 've made a change in the show . - What change ?
Don 't you worry .
I 've thought of a way to identify the killer .
I don 't know why I didn 't think of it before .
We have an eyewitness .
And if the maniac will be
in the audience tomorrow night ,
We 've got him !
What if he doesn 't come ?
Oh , he 'll come .
I 'm so tired . I 'm going to sleep .
" To sleep "
" Perchance to dream . "
" Aye , there 's the rub , "
" For in that sleep of death what dreams may come ...
" When we have shuffled off this mortal coil ...
Must give us pause . "
Is that you , mommy ?
Betty just had the same nightmare that
she used to have as child
But she didn 't know if it was just a dream ...
Or the memory of something that really happened .
What do you think of it ?
Any news ?
Relax , don 't worry . We 'll get him .
- But when ? - Any time now .
Six . Seven . Eight . Nine .
Any time now . Ten .
Eleven . Twelve . Thirteen .
Fourteen . Fifteen . Sixteen .
Seventeen . Eighteen . Nineteen .
Twenty . Go !
Now !
Police !
- I told you I 'd get him ! - You 're a genius !
It 's the policeman .
Extraordinary .
Why on earth would he do it ?
Shut up !
Just like your mother .
Your voice is the same as hers .
Your body , even your skin .
Oh , how much I loved her ! Shut up !
Shut up ! I didn 't want to kill her !
It was your mother !
She taught me a cruel little game ...
Of killing and torturing .
She wanted to be tied up !
I had to torture someone whilst she watched !
Only then could I have her .
I was her slave .
Calm down !
Sit down .
When I saw you the other night
I thought it was a miracle .
Sit still !
You know , it was easy .
It was easy to get rid of the other singer .
I was just hoping to start all over with you .
To continue those love games
I played with your mother !
But now it 's all over .
How could you love me , a monster ?
Close your eyes !
I don 't want you to look at me anymore .
Better die !
I want to disappear !
No one will ever find me .
I want to disappear
Can you smell it ? It 's petrol !
Are you scared ?
I am too Betty .
I 'm afraid of suffering .
Will you help me ?
Here .
Hold the gun . Higher .
To your left . To your left !
No !
Go right ! There !
Good . Now ... shoot !
Shoot !
Don 't you hate me after all I have done to you ?
Do you need another reason ?
All right then !
I killed your mother .
She wanted more blood , more cruelty
she was a whore !
And you know what ?
I enjoyed killing her .
Help ! I can 't get out !
Help !
Help ! Get me out of here !
Get me out of here !
Betty !
Quickly , quickly !
Come on ! Come on !
He 's dead !
Come on Marc , Paris means a lot to me .
We 'll make this Traviata unbelievable .
How do you want to play her ?
Tender ? Timid ?
Sensual ?
- Guten tag . - Guten tag .
Sensual . Let 's do sensual .
I knew it !
There has been a surprising development ...
In the case of the crime at the opera .
You 'll no doubt remember the
report that suspected maniac killer
Inspector Alan Santini
died in the fire that destroyed
one wing of the theater .
The police now inform us
that the charred remains ...
of the body they had presumed was Santini 's
are the remains of a theatrical mannequin .
Oh my God .
The authorities now realise
that Santini planned ...
his own fake death ...
in order to give
himself time to escape .
A nationwide hunt for Santini
is already underway .
He is considered to be extremely dangerous .
Betty , he 's not dead !
He 's alive !
He 's here ! Run !
For God 's sake , run !
I am like my mother .
I realise it now .
I wanted you to win .
I wanted you to kill him .
I 'm exactly like her .
Come . We must get away .
Come !
Let 's go before
someone finds the body .
Let 's go .
Don 't move !
Don 't move or I 'll shoot you !
Don 't move or I 'll kill you !
Don 't move !
Don 't move or I 'll blow your head off !
Son of a bitch !
You bastard !
Don 't move !
It 's not true ! I 'm not like my mother !
Nothing like her ! Nothing at all !
I am not a sadist !
I didn 't commit any crime !
I just wanted to free their souls !
Come on !
Hold onto him !
Clear the area !
Come on !
He wanted to kill you , huh ?
He wanted to kill you .
- Did you know we were coming ? - Yes , I did .
I saw your dogs running through the trees .
We 've been on his trail now for two days .
I saw you were talking to him .
What did you tell him ?
Nothing .
A lot of nonsense .
Lies .
Leave me alone .
Please leave me alone .
Betty no longer wanted to see anybody .
She wanted to escape altogether ...
Because she said she was different .
She didn 't even vaguely resemble others
any of them .
She liked the wind ,
she liked the butterflies
flowers , leaves ,
ears of wheat
insects
mountains
the rain .
You 're beautiful .
Go free .